gygan.com 2014-12-13

# Gygan | Watch Videos Online - Download or Stream Videos - Upload and Share Files

In General

At Gygan we know your number one concern is privacy. Therefore, we believe that we maintain the security and privacy standards you expect. Following are several safety and privacy issues you should be aware of when you browse our website. 

Personal Information

All of the information obtained by Gygan for the purposes of file sharing is kept strictly confidential. Gygan will never sell, rent or lease any of the personal information obtained through this website for any reason. Gygan will take every precaution to make sure that all the personal information that we receive is maintained and/or disposed of when necessary in a safe and secure manner. 

Children's Online Privacy

Gygan is concerned with the safety of children when they use the Internet. In accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 18. 

Site Copyrights

Unless otherwise noted, all materials including images, illustrations, designs, icons, photographs, written and other materials that appear as part of this website are copyrights, trademarks and/or other intellectual properties owned, controlled or licensed by Gygan. The website as a whole is protected by copyright and trade dress, all worldwide rights, titles and interests in and to which are owned by Gygan. The contents of our website, and the website as a whole, and the application are intended solely for the use of our website's visitors. You may download or copy the contents and other downloadable materials displayed on the site for your personal use only. No right, title or interest in any downloaded materials is transferred to you as a result of any such downloading or copying. You may not reproduce (except as noted above), publish, transmit, distribute, display, modify, create derivative works from, sell or participate in any sale of, or exploit in any way, in whole or in part, any of the contents of this site. 

The contents on this website may be used only as a service resource. Any other use, including reproduction, modification, distribution, transmission, republication, display or performance of the contents is strictly prohibited.

Personal Information Disclosure

We may forced to disclose your information if necessary to protect our legal rights or if the information relates to actual or threatened harmful conduct or potential threats to the physical safety of any person. The legal circumstancees will be evaluated individually in each case. Without a legal basis, no information will be disclosed.
